——你好吗?-喂，克里斯蒂娜在吗?
- Hello? - Hello Is Cristina there?
不，她现在不在。你要留言吗?
No, she's not available May I take a message?
抱歉，我是她小组里的一个朋友…哦，狗屎她的狗屎?
Sorry, I'm a friend of hers from group... Oh, shit From her shit?
听着，告诉她我是小组的我是查理她有我的号码她是你小组的?
Look, just tell her I'm from group I'm Charlie She's got my number She goes to your group?
我不应该……告诉她查理打电话来了我会照做的，查理，只要你告诉我这是什么组织那是嗜酒者互诫会吗?NA吗?
I shouldn't have... Just tell her that Charlie called I will do exactly that, Charlie, once you tell me what kind of group we're talking about Is it AA? NA?
你跟她描述的一模一样她在小组里谈论我?
You sound exactly like she describes you She talks about me in group?
我觉得我不能谈这个她怎么说我的?
I don't think I can really talk about that What does she say about me?
她非常爱你她爱我哪一点?
She loves you very much What does she love about me?
她喜欢你的创造力你喜欢艺术，电视和电影很多人都喜欢电影是的，但她说你喜欢恐怖片，而且你们有共同之处
She loves that you're creative You love art and TV and movies Lots of people love movies Yeah, but she says you love scary movies and that you guys have that in common
她很自豪能成为你的粉丝-真的吗?-是啊，那天她告诉我，她想知道…你最喜欢的恐怖电影是什么?
She's proud of making a fan out of you - She is? - Yeah She told me the other day, she wonders... what's your favorite scary movie?
《巴巴杜》这是对母亲和悲伤的奇妙思考有点花哨吧?
The Babadook It's an amazing meditation on motherhood and grief Isn't that a little fancy pants?
好吧，那是升华的恐怖嗯嗯"升华的恐怖"是什么意思? "?
Well, it's elevated horror Uh-huh What does that mean, "Elevated horror"?
这是一款带有复杂情感和主题基础的恐怖游戏，而不是一些带有整面墙的跳跃吓阻的蹩脚游戏听起来有点无聊你看过《刺杀》吗?
It's scary but with complex emotional and thematic underpinnings It's not just some schlocky, cheeseball nonsense with wall-to-wall jump scares Sounds kind of boring to me Have you ever seen Stab?
有一次，我大概12岁的时候在朋友家过夜你住在伍兹伯勒，却不知道《刺杀》?
Once, I think At a sleepover when I was, like, 12 You live in Woodsboro and you don't know Stab?
你妈妈很喜欢那部电影她总是在小组里谈论那部电影你还记得原著吗?
Your mother loves that movie She talks about it all the time in group How well do you remember the original?
我不知道，我是说，那是超级90年代，灯光太亮了，每个人都有奇怪的头发
I don't know I mean, it was super '90s It was really over-lit and everyone had weird hair
你还记得开头吗?
Do you remember the beginning?
不完全是，它是从一个杀人场景开始的，对吧?他们总是以杀人场景开始是的，没错没错是一个女孩独自在家
Not really It started with a kill scene, right? They always started with a kill scene Yeah, that's right That's right It's a girl at home, alone
她接错了电话，开始和凶手交谈，凶手让她玩了个游戏你想玩个游戏吗?泰拉?
She answers a wrong number and starts talking with the killer who makes her play a game Would you like to play a game... Tara?
系统武装
Systems armed
这他妈一点都不好笑，安柏我告诉过你，这不是安柏
This isn't fucking funny, Amber I told you, this isn't Amber
安波儿今晚看起来特别迷人她真的不应该把手机放在那里让别人来克隆你想要什么?
Amber's looking particularly fetching tonight She really shouldn't leave her phone lying around for anyone to clone What do you want?
我跟你说了，我想玩个游戏《刺杀》电影问答，三轮你报警，她就会死你问错问题，她就会死她父母不在家我15秒内就能到那房间
I told you, I want to play a game Stab movie trivia, three rounds You call the cops, she dies You get a question wrong, she dies Her parents aren't home I can be in that room in 15 seconds
你想要一个热身问题吗?
You want a warmup question?
我说了我不知道这些电影!
I told you I don't know these movies!
问我一些我知道的事问我关于它跟随问我关于遗传问我关于女巫在第一部《刺杀》中，
Ask me about something I do know Ask me about It Follows Ask me about Hereditary Ask me about The Witch In the first Stab movie,
哪个伍兹伯勒人被介绍为系列电影的主角?
what Woodsboro native was introduced as the franchise's main character?
西德尼·普雷斯科特!
It's Sidney Prescott!
她叫西德尼·普雷斯科特，住在榆树街，没错，你会做得很好的，第一个问题…不，我猜对了这应该算
It's Sidney Prescott and she lived on Elm Correct You see, you're gonna do great at this Okay, question one... No, I got that one right It should count
这一点任何人都能说对，西德尼在每一部电影里都有，除了最后一部，问题一:
Anyone could have gotten that one right Sidney's in every movie but the last one Question one:
《刺杀》系列电影根据的原著是谁写的?
Who wrote the original book that the Stab movies are based on?
电视上那个小妞!
The chick from TV!
《电视女郎》可不行，塔拉·盖尔·威瑟斯!
"The chick from TV" is not gonna cut it, Tara Gale Weathers!
是盖尔·威瑟斯，你个混蛋!
It is Gale Weathers, you motherfucker!
问题二:谁扮演了《刺杀1》开头接电话后被凶手肢解的蠢婊子?
Correct Amber might live to see the sunrise Question two: Who played the dumb bitch at the beginning of Stab 1 who answers the phone and gets carved up by the killer?
去你妈的这就是你的答案吗?
Fuck you Is that the answer you're going with?
不回答就是错误的答案，塔拉时间到了滴答，滴答，滴答，滴答，滴答…希瑟·格雷厄姆!
A non-answer counts as a wrong answer, Tara Time's running out Tick-tock, tick-tock, tick-tock, tick-tock, tick-tock... Heather Graham!
正确的!现在是最后一个问题
Correct! You pulled that one out Now for the final question:
《刺杀1》中的凶手是谁?
Who was the killer in Stab 1?
我知道这个，你他妈的是比利·卢米斯!
I know this one, you fuck It's Billy Loomis!
他是西德尼的男朋友，由卢克·威尔逊扮演，我抓到你了，混蛋!
He was Sidney's boyfriend, and he was played by Luke Wilson, and I got you, asshole!
我得到它!我答对了!
I got it! I got it right!
抱歉，泰拉，但这是不对的什么?
Oh, I'm sorry, Tara, but that's just not correct What?
不，不，它是它是对的正确答案是比利·卢米斯和斯图·马赫在最初的《刺杀》中有两个杀手恐怕现在要死了一个人不，不，安柏，我来了
No, no, it is It is That is right The correct answer is Billy Loomis and Stu Macher There are two killers in the original Stab I'm afraid someone's got to die now No, no, no Amber, I'm coming
他妈的,他妈的,他妈的
Fuck, fuck, fuck
系统武装
Systems armed
警察马上就来了，混蛋!
The police are on their way, asshole!
所有系统解除武装
All systems disarmed
系统武装
Systems armed
所有系统解除武装-哦，我的上帝没有系统武装所有系统解除武装所有系统解除武装所有系统解除武装系统武装
-All systems disarmed -Oh, my God No Systems armed All systems disarmed Systems armed All systems disarmed Systems armed
喂?
Hello?
顺便问个问题，泰拉别说了你觉得我在你重新武装之前就进了你家吗?
Bonus question, Tara Please stop Do you think I made it inside your house before you could rearm?
的帮助!
Help!
对不起,小姐?
Excuse me, miss?
-你刚吃了什么?-你的壮阳药祝你现在能勃起你…你是我的壮阳药
- What'd you just take? - Your boner pills Good luck getting it up now You... You are my boner pills
不不
No No
你没事吧?
You okay?
是的你不用一直盯着我我不容易碎是的，这我知道
Yes You don't have to check on me all the time I'm not breakable Yeah, this I know
狗屎
Shit
- - - - - -山姆?-嘿，怎么了?
- Sam? - Hey What's going on?
塔拉……袭击了什么?她是…她还活着，但情况很糟她…刺刺?他妈的什么?
Tara... was attacked What? Is she... She's alive, but in bad shape She was... stabbed Stabbed? What the fuck?
她挺过了手术，医生说一切都很顺利。她现在正在休息。我知道你们俩关系不太好，但是…我在路上了她会没事的，萨姆我们很快会再见的
She made it through surgery and the doctor said it went well She's resting now I know you guys aren't on the best terms, but... I'm on my way She's gonna be okay, Sam We'll see you soon
嘿,等一下,韦斯!
Hey, wait, Wes!
是吗?
Yeah?
他们知道是谁干的吗?
Do they know who did this?
你还是过来吧维斯她说那是个戴着鬼脸面具的人
It's probably better if you just come here Wes She said it was someone in a fucking Ghostface mask
我妹妹被袭击了我得走了等等，嘿!我和你一起去不，里奇…不，萨姆，我和你一起去-好的-好的
My sister was attacked I gotta go Wait, hey! I'm going with you No, Richie... No, Sam I'm coming with you -Okay -Okay Yeah
注意，黑豹队提醒大家，出于公共安全考虑明天所有的课程和学校活动都将取消那是山姆-她要来了?-是的，看着一切变得更糟
Attention, Panthers A reminder that all classes and school activities are canceled tomorrow due to public safety concerns That was Sam - She's coming? - Yeah Watch everything get worse
听着，我想说的是，现在发生了这么多事，我觉得是时候让我们的关系进入下一个，最亲密的阶段了他想让我接受他的"找我的家人"的请求
Listen, all I'm saying is, with everything going on right now, I think it's time we take our relationship to the next, most intimate level He wants me to accept his Find My Fam request
这是最明智的选择，因为一个潜在的杀手还在逍遥法外你知道我在哪里，我也知道你在哪里你可以像个嫉妒的男朋友一样跟踪我
It's the smartest option with a would-be killer on the loose You know exactly where I am and I know exactly where you are Aw, you can stalk me like a jealous boyfriend
你可以像个吃醋的男朋友一样跟踪我是因为你俩还没做爱吗?
And you can stalk me like a jealous boyfriend Is this because you two aren't having sex yet?
你提出了一个很好的观点并不是说我想听起来像个想和女朋友上床的普通运动员很好!
You actually bring up a very good point Not that I want to sound like a stereotypical jock trying to get into his girlfriend's pants Great!
别这么做，丽芙外面有个疯子你让自己更难找到删除社交媒体，用手机摄像头拍照，关闭GPS是的，非常感谢，爱德华·斯诺登
Don't do it, Liv There's a psycho out there You make yourself harder to find Delete social media, tape over your phone camera, disable GPS Yes, thank you very much, Edward Snowden
事实上，你母亲刚刚审问了我关于塔拉的谋杀未遂，很有趣我相信她会问每个人的我是说，幽灵脸回来了媒体还是没说幽灵脸
Actually, your mother just interrogated me about Tara's attempted murder, which was very fun I'm sure she's asking everybody I mean, Ghostface is back The press still isn't saying Ghostface
我妈不想引起恐慌它会在第二次或第三次杀人时泄露出来杰西，明迪，没有第一次杀人泰拉还活着这意味着她还是有可能死的
My mom doesn't want to cause a panic It'll get out by the second or third killing Jesus, Mindy, there wasn't a first killing Tara's alive That means she could still die
-怎么回事?-或者凶手会回来找她妈的!明迪，别这样，我只是告诉你，举起手来，好吗?胡椒喷雾，电击枪，女友驱蚊剂，很好谢谢
- What the fuck? - Or the killer could come back for her Fuck! Mindy, come on I'm just telling you, arm up, okay? Pepper spray, check Taser, check Girlfriend repellent, check Nice Thank you
哦，该死那是…文斯?
Oh, shit Is that... Vince?
等等去年夏天你勾搭上的那个变态?
Wait The creep you hooked up with last summer?
是的，他和我还有塔拉一起工作他和塔拉一起工作?
Yeah, he worked with me and Tara He worked with Tara?
过去几周他一直在我的Instagram上刷，发一些最恶心的东西也许是时候把他介绍给霍布斯和肖了
He's been stalking my Instagram the last couple weeks, posting the creepiest shit Probably time to introduce him to Hobbs and Shaw
在治安官面前煽动暴力也许不是个好主意看起来他要走了谢谢，伙计们
Maybe not the best idea to incite violence right in front of the sheriff Looks like he's leaving Thanks anyway, boys
泰拉说她反抗得很厉害你踢足球时受伤了当然了泰拉醒了她刚发短信说我要去医院你们一起来吗?
Tara says she fought back hard You've got bruises From football practice Oh, sure Tara's awake She just texted I'm going to the hospital You guys coming?
-我去不了，晚点见好吧
-Yeah -Yeah I can't, but I'll meet you guys later All right
其实我没看过《刺杀》你没看过《刺杀》吗?
I've actually never seen Stab You've never seen Stab?
就连去年出版的那本也没有吗?
Not even the one that came out last year?
我也没看过《乱世佳人》，但我不认为它对我的电影教育有什么影响。《刺杀》的大部分电影都是基于这里发生的事情。
I've never seen Gone With the Wind either, but I don't consider it like a huge hole in my cinematic education Most of the Stab movies are based on things that happened here Define "things"
之类的……一个叫比利·卢米斯的家伙和他的朋友带着万圣节的鬼面具在一群高中生身上行凶你是说在万圣节的时候吗?
Things like... a guy named Billy Loomis and his friend carved up a bunch of high-school kids while wearing this Halloween ghost mask You mean like in Halloween?
不，不像万圣节那样
No Not like in Halloween
-听起来很像万圣节-好吧，有点像万圣节每隔十年左右，就会有个白痴想出个好主意，戴上面具，杀了他的朋友，然后也出名了
-Sounds a lot like Halloween -All right, it's a little like Halloween And every decade or so, some idiot gets the bright idea to put on the mask, kill his friends, and get famous, too
上次是在2011年我们是自愿来的吗?
The last time it happened was in 2011 And we came here voluntarily?
我得确保泰拉没事是的，当然了我得确保我们不会被某个疯子切成肉片他们看到13号星期五就想"你知道吗?
Well, I got to make sure Tara's okay Yes, of course And I got to make sure we don't get sliced up by some lunatic who saw Friday the 13th and thought, "You know what?
那个叫杰森的家伙，他有一些不错的主意"
That Jason guy, he's got some pretty solid ideas"
我能问你一个问题吗?
Can I just ask you one question, though?
是的你知道为什么戴着面具的人想要杀你妹妹吗?
Yeah Do you have any idea why someone wearing that mask would want to kill your sister?
没有
No
你感觉怎么样?
How are you feeling?
你来了我当然来了这是我男朋友，里奇很高兴见到你如果我打扰了很抱歉见到你很高兴你好你好-谢谢你打电话来-当然
You came Of course I came This is my boyfriend, Richie It's so nice to meet you I'm so sorry if I'm intruding Nice to meet you, too Hi Hi -Thank you for calling -Of course
看看你的头发!我喜欢这是查德和明迪，一对双胞胎还有韦斯我曾经照顾过他们我总是喜欢这样被介绍
Look at your hair! I like it These are Chad and Mindy, the twins And Wes I used to babysit them all Which is always how I like to be introduced
安柏嘿，嗨，很高兴见到你-嗨，我是里奇-嗨-妈妈呢?-她在伦敦开会她之前给我打过电话是的，打了十分钟
And Amber Hey Hi Nice to see you -Hi I'm Richie -Hi - Where's Mom? - She's stuck at a conference in London She called me earlier Yeah, for all of ten minutes
听着，泰拉真的很累了也许我们应该给她一些空间-好的-好的
Look, guys, Tara's really tired Maybe we should just give her some space -Yeah -Yeah
不是你，山姆我想让你留下-但其他的-如果你不介意的话，我今晚可以睡在这里我真的很想好的-你有多余的吸入器吗?-是的，我会没事的
Not you, Sam I want you to stay Okay -But the rest -Yeah If it's okay with you, I could sleep here tonight I'd really like that Okay - Do you have your extra inhaler? - Yeah, I'll be fine Okay
亲爱的?好的，我就在外面谢谢再见
Honey? Okay, I'll just be right outside Thank you Bye
萨姆，我很害怕，我知道没事的
Sam, I was so scared I know It's okay
她是个什么样的人，那个妹妹?
So what is she like, the sister?
山姆?山姆真酷你这么说只是因为她让你穿了一年精灵宝可梦连体衣上床那是真的那是真的不，相信我，山姆一点都不酷
Sam? Sam is so cool You only say that because she let you wear Pokemon onesies to bed for a year That's true That's a true statement No, trust me, Sam is not cool
她爸爸离开了她妈妈泰拉八岁，山姆十三岁的时候就离开了山姆开始耍脾气，惹上了警察然后，在山姆十八岁生日的时候，她把幽灵们都留下了
Her dad left her mom Walks right out when Tara's eight, Sam's 13 Sam started acting out, getting in trouble with the cops And then, on Sam's 18th birthday, she leaves Ghosts them all
也许山姆变了我只是不想看到泰拉再次受到伤害所以呢，你现在在保护泰拉不受她亲妹妹的伤害?
Maybe Sam's changed I just don't want to see Tara hurt again So what, you're protecting Tara from her own sister now?
总得有人好吧，所以没人配得上她现在她的家庭也成了禁区?
Well, someone has to Okay, so no guys are good enough for her and now her family's off-limits, too?
动机是"如果我得不到她，别人也得不到"
Mm, motive "If I can't have her, no one can"
——什么?-我们都知道你喜欢塔拉好吧拜托，明蒂但我们都是嫌疑犯
- What? - We all know you have a crush on Tara Okay Come on, Mindy But we're all suspects
除了也许丽芙-谢谢-你太无聊了，不像个疯子丽芙你想喝一杯吗?
Except maybe Liv -Thank you -You're way too boring to be a psycho Yo, Liv You want a real drink?
还是你喜欢坐在这张儿童桌?
Or are you happy sitting at this kids' table?
听着，丑八怪迈克尔·迈尔斯，那只是个夏日风流韵事毫无意义-我在跟你说话吗?-我不管你在跟谁说话-丽芙，我们走-别跟她说话!
Listen up, Uglier Michael Myers, it was a summer fling It meant nothing - Was I talking to you? - I don't care who you're talking to -Liv, let's go -Don't talk to her!
-我不想听到你的声音-闭上你的嘴最好他妈的闭上你的嘴离开这里，否则我要报警了快走!
-I don't want to hear your voice -Shut your mouth Better shut the fuck up Get out of here or I'm calling the cops Go!
-我会很快见到你的，甜心-嘿，伙计，操你妈的你们也是孩子!我们走吧!
-I'll see you soon, sweetheart -Hey, man, fuck you You kids, too! Let's go!
你看到了吗?
Did you see that shit?
去他妈的酒吧，伙计
Fuck this bar, man
去你妈的
Fuck you
他妈的烦!
Fuck it!
他妈的什么?
What the fuck?
是你吗，帅哥?嗯?
Is that you, pretty boy? Huh?
滚出我的车!
Get out of my fucking car!
嘿-你还好吗?-是啊只是做了个噩梦你在看什么?
Hey - You okay? - Yeah Just a bad dream What are you watching?
《刺杀》在Netflix上播出
Stab is on Netflix
什么?我要做好准备我得去找点吃的好吧
What? I want to be prepared I got to go find something to eat Yeah, okay
你好吗，萨姆?
How you doing, Sam?
抗精神病药没以前那么有效了，对吧?
Antipsychotics aren't working as well as they used to, are they?
去你妈的你不能逃避自己的身份，萨姆我只是想帮你你打算什么时候告诉她这一切的原因?
Fuck you You can't run from who you are, Sam I'm just trying to help Hey, when are you gonna tell her why all this is happening?
你好你好,萨曼莎
Hello Hello, Samantha
这是谁?
Who is this?
一个知道你家庭秘密的人你就是那个伤害我妹妹的人?
Someone who knows your little family secret You're the fuck who hurt my sister?
她不是我唯一要伤害的人我总得想办法让你回来，不是吗?
She's not the only one I'm gonna hurt I had to get you to come back here somehow, didn't I?
你想耍我吗，混蛋?
You want to fuck with me, asshole?
我就在这里来接我很高兴
I'm right here Come and get me With pleasure
的帮助!
Help!
的帮助!的帮助!
Help! Help!
谁来帮帮我，他要杀了我!
Somebody help me, he's trying to kill me!
这是怎么呢你没事的在休息室有人想杀我!
What's going on? You're okay Somebody tried to kill me in the break room!
我在主街的酒吧外发现了一具尸体，然后你在这里被袭击了你说电话是安珀的号码打的?
I've got a body outside a bar on Main, and then you get attacked here You said the call came from Amber's number?
所以呢?我们知道他袭击塔拉的时候打过我的电话你就是凶手这一切发生的时候你在哪里?
So? We know he called on my phone before when he attacked Tara Or, and I'm just spit-balling here... you're the killer And where were you when all this happened?
我是……看网飞-哦，是的，超级可靠的不在场证明，兄弟-那你去哪了?
I was... watching Netflix -Ooh, yeah Super-solid alibi, bro -So where were you?
我在警局审问安珀和她朋友是的，我一听到就来了但是，你知道，网飞公司的不在场证明也很好你们两个，住手
I was questioning Amber and her friends at the sheriff's station Yeah, I came as soon as I heard But, you know, the Netflix alibi is good, too Both of you, stop it
你会派更多警察去监视她的房间，对吧?
You're gonna put more cops on her room, right?
是的我可以把你转移到私人楼层文森警官知道他在做什么，你会安全的就像我们现在做的那样?
Yes And I can move you to a private floor Deputy Vinson knows what he's doing, you'll be safe Like we've been so far?
萨曼莎，我们出去吧
Samantha, let's step outside
很高兴见到你，希克斯副警长-多有趣的回忆啊-我是"希克斯警长"我也记得你…还有你给你家人带来的所有麻烦你在这里帮不了什么忙
Nice to see you, Deputy Hicks -So many fun memories -It's "Sheriff" Hicks I remember you, too... and all the trouble you used to cause your family Your presence here is not helping
所以也许当太阳升起的时候，你和你的男朋友可以离开，把这个问题留给真正关心这个社区的人
So maybe when the sun comes up, you and your boyfriend can hit the road and leave it to people who actually care about this community
她还是个快乐的人你还好吗?
Well, she remains a delight Are you okay?
能让我们单独谈谈吗?我要和泰拉谈谈来吧，奈飞，我们走
Would you mind giving us a second? I need to talk to Tara Come on, Netflix, let's go
你还记得爸爸离开的时候吗?
Do you remember when Dad left?
部分,确定
Parts, sure
我才八岁那有什么关系?
I was eight What does that have to do with anything?
这与它有关
It has to do with it
你还记得……妈妈以前把这些盒子放在阁楼上吗?
Do you remember how... Mom used to keep those boxes up in the attic?
我去过一次……我13岁的时候，在找圣诞礼物的时候我发现了她高中时留下的日记-萨姆，这是…-拜托，我必须这么做
Well, I was up there once... When I was 13, looking for Christmas presents And I found these old diaries that she kept from high school - Sam, what is... - Please I have to do this
所以我找到了这些旧日记我知道这是错的，但我还是看了一些因为妈妈在高中的时候怀了我，我想知道她和爸爸是怎么在一起的一定很酷
So I found these old diaries And I knew it was wrong, but I read some anyway because Mom got pregnant with me in high school, and I thought it could be cool to find out how she and Dad got together
那一定很浪漫所以我读了一些只是不浪漫
How romantic it must have been So I read some Only it wasn't romantic
妈妈在和爸爸约会，但是…她爱上了另一个男人…然后他让她怀孕了她告诉爸爸这是他的，所以他才在高三向她求婚萨姆，你在说什么?
Mom was dating Dad, but... she was in love with this other guy... and he got her pregnant She told Dad it was his, and that's why he proposed senior year Sam, what are you talking about?
我坐在阁楼里……我13岁…我才发现我爸爸不是我爸爸
And I'm sitting there, in this attic... and I'm 13... and I just found out my dad isn't my dad
所以我去了妈妈的卧室，对着她大喊大叫，还把这本日记塞到她脸上，我甚至没有意识到……爸爸就站在我身后
So I go find Mom in her bedroom, and I'm screaming at her and shoving this diary in her face, and I didn't even realize... that Dad was standing right behind me
他不知道
He didn't know
他当时就从我这里知道了
He found out right then from me
他那晚离开是因为我不不，山姆…妈妈永远不会原谅我然后她让我发誓永远不会告诉你，因为你还小所以我改变了
He left that night I'm the reason he left No No, Sam... Mom never forgave me Then she made me promise never to tell you because you were so young And that's why I changed
我对你疏远又奇怪
and I got distant and weird with you
然后我出去，我开始嗑所有我能弄到的药直到我再也受不了了然后我离开了小镇我再也不想和你在一起了，塔拉
And I went out and I started doing every drug that I could get my hands on until I couldn't take it anymore and I left town I just couldn't be around you anymore, Tara
不仅因为那晚我毁了我们的家庭，还因为…那些日记告诉了我谁是我的亲生父亲
Not only because I destroyed our family that night, but because... those diaries told me who my real father was
是比利·卢米斯有人知道了，我想这就是你受伤的原因我真他妈抱歉，我没告诉你然后就跑了-我很抱歉-把泰拉弄出来
It was Billy Loomis And somebody knows, and I think that's why you got hurt And I'm so fucking sorry that I never told you and then I ran away -I'm so sorry -Get out Tara
你已经离开五年了…整整五年然后我被捅了一刀，你就想回来把这一切都推给我?
You're gone for five years... Five whole years And then I get stabbed and you want to come back and drop all this shit on me?
我以为我在保护你保护我不受什么伤害?
I thought I was protecting you Protecting me from what?
真相?
The truth?
不不,我……求你了，泰拉-山姆-山姆，我要你他妈的滚出去-我很抱歉-山姆-求你他妈的滚出去!
-No No, I... Please, Tara -Sam -Sam, I need you to get the fuck out -I'm so sorry -Sam -Please Get the fuck out!
嘿，嘿，嘿没事的，是我你在门口偷听吗?
Hey, hey, hey It's okay, it's me Were you listening at the door?
不，不，当然不是好吧，是的，我在门口偷听你不会被吓到…我的亲生父亲是个连环杀手?
No, no, of course not Okay, yeah, I was listening at the door It doesn't freak you out... that my real father was a serial killer?
我的意思是……是的，很好，是的好吧，那你走吧我明白了我要留下来，弄清楚我不能把你留在这里，萨姆你知道恐怖电影里的那种角色
I mean... yeah A great deal, yeah Okay, well, then go I get it I just got to stay and figure it out I'm not leaving you here, Sam You know that part in horror movies
你想对角色大喊大叫让他们聪明点然后滚出去吗?
where you want to yell at the characters to be smart and get the fuck out?
就是这个部分了，里奇你他妈该滚了
This is that part, Richie You should get the fuck out
但我住
But I'm staying
我爱你
I love you
-你真是个笨蛋-我真是个笨蛋所以…你妹妹不肯跟你说话警察也不会帮我们下一步怎么办?
-You're such a dumbass -I'm such a dumbass So... your sister won't talk to you The police aren't gonna help What's our next move?
我们去找专家谈谈
We go talk to an expert
.．.周二和周三这里的气温都是55度左右，下周也会是60度左右而就在一天晚上，一名当地青少年在家中遭到袭击
...a few temperatures here Tuesday, Wednesday in the mid-50s, and then finally we'll see those mid-60s returning into next week And just one night after a local teen was attacked in her home
一名身穿鬼脸服装的袭击者，朱迪·希克斯警长已经证实又有两起深夜袭击事件使伍兹伯勒市陷入混乱第一名受害者，文森特·施耐德，被发现死亡
by an assailant in a Ghostface costume, Sheriff Judy Hicks has now confirmed two more late-night attacks that have left Woodsboro reeling The first victim, Vincent Schneider, was found dead
另一名尚未透露姓名的受害者在伍兹伯勒综合医院内遭到袭击，但她没有受伤
behind the Corner Pocket Pool Hall A second victim, as yet unnamed, was attacked inside Woodsboro General Hospital, but she escaped without injuries
不用说，伍兹伯勒今天处于高度戒备状态……洛克菲勒广场1-A工作室现场直播…早上好，我是盖尔·威瑟斯在我们开始之前，我想告诉你们一个小故事
Needless to say, Woodsboro is on high alert today... Live from Studio 1-A in Rockefeller Plaza... Good morning I'm Gale Weathers Before we dive in, I want to tell you a little story
今天早上在去录音室的路上，我停下来在一家杂货店买了一块培根、鸡蛋和奶酪，这已经是典型的纽约风格了……走开!
that happened on the way to the studio this morning I stopped to get a bacon, egg and cheese at a bodega, already a quintessentially New York... Go away!
很抱歉打扰你，莱利先生!
Sorry to bother you, Mr Riley!
我们只是想问你几个问题我不接受采访我们不是在找采访给我个理由让我找你谈谈我是比利·卢米斯的女儿
We just want to ask you a few questions I don't give interviews We're not looking for an interview Give me one good reason why I should talk to you I'm Billy Loomis's daughter
我跟你说话的理由太可怕了我叫萨曼莎·卡朋特昨晚在医院里被人袭击了就在那之前的一晚，我妹妹被捅了七刀
That's a terrible reason for me to talk to you My name is Samantha Carpenter I was attacked last night at the hospital The night before that, my sister was stabbed seven times
我知道你知道那是什么感觉我只是想保护我的家人五分钟这就是我唯一的要求我给你两分钟我将错过我喜欢的节目
I know you know what that's like I'm just trying to protect my family Five minutes That's all I'm asking I'll give you two minutes I'm missing a show I like
如果我威胁说要留刘海，你就劝导我，盖尔·威瑟斯-你们俩不是…-是
If I ever threaten to get bangs, stage an intervention Gale Weathers -Weren't you two... -Yeah
他是谁?
Who's he?
这是里奇，我的男朋友你认识他多久了?
This is Richie, my boyfriend How long have you known him?
六个月?
Six months?
你刚认识他时，他知道你爸爸是谁吗?
Did he know who your dad was when you met?
你对伍兹伯勒和鬼脸谋杀案有兴趣吗?
Express any interest in Woodsboro or the Ghostface killings?
你到底在说什么?
What the hell are you talking about?
凶手痴迷于《刺杀》系列电影，对吧?
Your killer's obsessed with the Stab movies, right?
要想在《刺杀》中幸存是有一定规则的相信我，我知道第一条规则
Well, there are certain rules to surviving a Stab movie Believe me, I know Rule number one:
永远不要相信爱的对象他们看起来很贴心，关心，支持欢迎进入第三幕，他们会把你的脑袋拧下来塔拉被袭击时我和萨姆在莫德斯托
Never trust the love interest They seem sweet, caring, supportive Then welcome to act 3, where they're trying to rip your head off I was with Sam in Modesto when Tara was attacked
让我猜猜，当她在医院被袭击时，你刚好在另一个房间里，而她恰好下落不明我要听那个混蛋萨姆·艾略特说这些吗?
And let me guess, you were just in the other room, conveniently unaccounted for when she was attacked at the hospital Do I have to take this from shitty Sam Elliott over here, or what?
规则二:
Rule number two:
凶手的动机总是和过去我和比利有关系的事有关没错，但为什么要杀那个叫文斯的家伙?
The killer's motive is always connected to something in the past I'm related to Billy Right, but then why kill that random Vince guy?
这是你要弄清楚的第三条规则，这是最重要的规则
That's for you to figure out And rule number three, and this is the most important rule:
第一个受害者总是有一个杀手是其中一员的朋友圈你姐姐有一个很亲密的朋友圈吗?
The first victim always has a friend group that the killer is a part of Does your sister have a close-knit group of friends?
是的那就去找那个凶手如果你能找出他们这么做的原因，你就能找出下一个目标所以帮我们帮我们找出谁是幕后黑手
Yeah She does Then look for the killer there If you can find out why they're doing this, you can figure out who's next So help us Help us figure out who is behind this
你在开玩笑吗?我被捅了九刀，有永久性神经损伤，还有一点轻微的跛行你以为我想再来一次吗?
You kidding me? I've been stabbed nine times I've got permanent nerve damage and a fun little limp You think I want to do that again?
你刚说过总是回到过去，对吧?
You just said it always goes back to the past, right?
所以如果我有危险…那意味着你有危险来吧我们一起来
So if I'm in danger... that means you're in danger Come on Let's do this together
你的时间到了，耶稣!
Your time's up Jesus!
是啊，他在电影里更有趣
Yeah, he's way more fun in the movies
好了,接下来是什么?
Okay, what's next?
非常感谢你，凯文，接下来是当地的天气，和老朋友重聚的利弊
The friends Thanks so much for that, Kevin Coming up after our local weather, the pros and cons of reuniting with old friends
喂?
Hello?
嘿，希德，是我杜威吗?
Hey, Sid, it's me Dewey?
我的天哪我们多久没见了?
Oh, my God How long has it been?
我只是想在送孩子们去学校之前先跑一趟你好吗?
I'm just trying to get a run in before I take the girls to school How are you?
我很好，真的很好你呢?马克怎么样?
I'm good, really good How are you? How's Mark?
我想我会留下他治安官的事怎么样了?
I think I'll keep him How are things in the sheriff's business?
他们……-他们很好，但是，希德…-你最近和盖尔聊过吗?
They're... - They're fine But, Sid... - Have you talked to Gale lately?
我知道你们的结局不太好，但是…Sid……这是再次发生
No Not in a couple years I know things didn't end well with you guys, but... Sid... it's happening again
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
一个戴着鬼面面具的白痴目前已经三次袭击了一次死了这次感觉有点不一样
Some idiot in a Ghostface mask Three attacks so far One dead Something about this one just feels different
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
我很好，你知道我的是的我知道所以我才问你我很好我只是…希望你在上面安全你有枪吗?
I'm fine, you know me Yeah I do That's why I'm asking I'm fine I just... want you to be safe up there Do you have a gun?
我是他妈的西德尼·普雷斯科特当然我有枪
I'm Sidney fucking Prescott Of course I have a gun
很好很好盖尔知道吗?
Good That's good Does Gale know?
不，她是我的下一个目标但是，希德，答应我
No, she's my next call But, Sid, promise me:
不管你在新闻上听到或看到什么，都不要来这里无意冒犯，杜威，我再也不想踏进那个小镇了好，杜威…
No matter what you hear or what you see on the news, don't come here No offense, Dewey I have no intention of ever setting foot in that town again Good Dewey...
不管凶手在找谁，我很高兴有你保护他们
whoever this killer's after, I'm glad they have you to protect them
注意安全，好吗?
You be safe, okay?
能听到你的声音真好你也是，希德
Will do It's good to hear your voice You, too, Sid
来吧振作起来，杜威
Come on Get it together, Dewey
也许我不该发那张笑脸
Probably shouldn't have sent the smiley face
天啊，他来了
Holy shit He came
我决定暂时协助你的调查谢谢
I've decided to temporarily assist you in your investigation Thank you
听着，就算他洗了澡也不代表他就该有枪
Look, just because that guy showered doesn't mean he should have a gun
你怎么这么了解《刺杀》
How do you know so much about Stab?
兰迪是我们的叔叔安息吧
Runs in her family Randy was our uncle RIP
你说把所有人都带来
You said to bring everybody
哇,嫌疑人!
Woo, suspects!
我哥哥会很骄傲的玛莎·杜威!这就跟你问声好！
My brother would be so proud Hey, Martha Dewey! Hi!
你看起来……
You look...
是的-你妻子怎么样?-好的，妈妈，我们很好谢谢好了，孩子们，玩得开心
Yeah - How's the wife? - Okay, Mom, we're good Thank you All right, kids, have fun
我让明迪给大家打电话，因为…
I asked Mindy to call everybody here, because...
有些事我得告诉你让我把话说清楚你是说你是比利·卢米斯的女儿，然后呢，我们其中一个就是凶手?
there's something I have to tell you So let me get this straight You're saying that you're the daughter of Billy Loomis, and, what, that one of us is the killer?
凶手告诉我他知道我的秘密他袭击塔拉是为了引诱我回来但为什么马上就去杀了一个跟踪丽芙的混蛋?
The killer told me he knew my secret He attacked Tara to lure me back here But then why immediately go and murder some douche-nozzle that was stalking Liv?
为什么必须是我们中的一员?
And why does it have to be one of us?
杜威警官呢?也许他就是凶手没有冒犯的意思没事，但我的动机是什么?
What about Deputy Dewey here? Maybe he's the killer No offense None taken, but what's my motive?
你被捅了无数刀，被你著名的妻子甩了还爬进了一个瓶子里我想可以肯定地说你是嫌疑犯名单上的人也许你就是凶手因为伤口很深
You got stabbed a billion times, got dumped by your famous wife and crawled into a bottle I think it's safe to say you're on the suspect list Well, maybe you're the killer Because that cut deep
那个混蛋有联系，我谷歌了他妈妈是莱斯利·马赫斯图·马赫的妹妹斯图·马赫是谁?
That douche-nozzle is connected I googled him His mom is Leslie Macher -Stu Macher's sister -Who's Stu Macher?
他是比利·卢米斯的同伙真是疯了好吧好吧前三起袭击都是针对和最初的凶手有关系的人天哪他在写反串!
He's Billy Loomis's accomplice A real loony tune Okay Okay So the first three attacks are all on people related to the original killers Oh, my God He's making a requel!
一个什么?
A what?
还记得去年上映的电影《刺杀》吗?
Or a legacyquel Fans are torn on the terminology God Please speak English Remember the Stab movie that came out last year?
哦,耶!就是那个《刀锋喋血》的导演，对吧?
Oh, yeah! The one the Knives Out guy directed, right?
我真的很喜欢你当然喜欢你的品味很差我讨厌你重点是，《刺杀》的铁杆粉丝都很讨厌你上4chan和Dreadit，
I actually really liked that one Of course you did You have terrible taste I hate you The point is, the hard-core Stab fans hated it You go on 4chan and Dreadit,
他们谈论的都是《刺杀8》是如何毁了他们的童年，他们是如何为了提升自己而加入社会评论的，主角是玛丽·苏
all they're talking about is how Stab 8 pissed on their childhoods How they crammed in social commentary just to elevate it How the main character's a Mary Sue
玛丽苏是什么?-你真的不想知道过度恐惧有什么问题吗?
- What's a Mary Sue? - You really don't want to know What's wrong with elevated horror?
我是说，乔丹·皮尔很明显，但那不是《刺杀》《刺杀》电影是超恐怖的侦探小说，就这样-拜托，这只是一部电影-不，不是
I mean, Jordan Peele fucking rules Obviously, but that's not Stab Real Stab movies are meta slasher whodunits, full stop -Come on, it's just a movie -No, it's not
对一些人来说，原版是他们最喜欢的东西让他们喜欢恐怖的电影在他们十岁的时候爸爸妈妈给他们看的把他们团结在一起的电影
To some people, the original is their favorite thing in the world The movie that made them love horror That Mom or Dad showed them when they were ten that bonded them together
上帝保佑那些稍微破坏了他的特殊记忆的人那些拍了一部他们认为不尊重的电影的人听起来像是凶手在写他自己版本的《刺杀8》，但是作为一种请求
And God help anyone who slightly fucks with that special memory Who makes a movie they think disrespects it It sounds like our killer is writing his own version of Stab 8, but doing it as a requel
是哪一个?
Which is?
《黑色圣诞节》、《儿童游戏》、《Flatliners》……那玩意不管用
See, you can't just reboot a franchise from scratch anymore The fans won't stand for it Black Christmas, Child's Play, Flatliners... that shit doesn't work
但你不能直接拍续集，要么你得创造一些新东西但不能太新，要么网络就他妈的疯了，它必须是一个持续的故事线的一部分，
But you can't just do a straight sequel, either You got to build something new But not too new, or the Internet goes bug-fucking nuts It has to be part of an ongoing story line,
新的主要角色，是的，但由传统角色支持并与之相关，不完全是重启，也不完全是续集
even if the story shouldn't have been ongoing in the first place New main characters, yes, but supported by and related to legacy characters Not quite a reboot, not quite a sequel
比如新的《万圣节》、《电锯惊魂》、《终结者》、《侏罗纪公园》、《捉鬼敢死队》……操，甚至星球大战!
Like the new Halloween, Saw, Terminator, Jurassic Park, Ghostbusters... fuck, even Star Wars!
它总是，总是回到原来的样子!
It always, always goes back to the original!
你是说我在看他妈同人小说吗?
Are you telling me that I'm caught in the middle of fan-fucking-fiction?
不只是在中间，山姆你才是明星
Not just in the middle, Sam You're the star
所以，不是说得太细，但是，根据requel的规则…下一个是谁?
So, not to put too fine a point on it, but, according to requel rules... who's next?
按照这个模式，不管是谁，肯定和之前来过的人有联系
Going by the pattern, whoever it is has to be connected to someone that came before
我开始后悔来这里了天哪，我妈妈是其中的一个角色没人在乎那些烂片，韦斯你很安全
I'm starting to regret coming here Jesus, my mom was a character in one of them No one cares about the shitty inferior sequels, Wes You're safe
兰迪是我们的叔叔，你和我可能完蛋了等等什么?
With Randy as our uncle, though, you and I are probably screwed Wait What?
或者你是凶手，而这整段精心设计的独白只是为了掩盖你的踪迹我想现在凶手是谁已经很清楚了谁?
Or you're the killer, and this whole elaborate monologue is just to cover your tracks I think it's pretty clear who the killer is at this point Who?
你这完全说得通-确实说得通-是啊
You It makes perfect requel sense -That actually does make a lot of sense -Yeah
去你妈的-汽车旅馆见-萨姆，等等萨姆，等等这些电影的第一条规则就是不要分开!
Fuck this -Meet you back at the motel -Sam, wait Sam, wait The first fucking rule of these movies is don't split up!
那女孩的胆量，对吧?
The nerve of that girl, right?
我现在真的没心情山姆，山姆，山姆有个杀手在逍遥法外他在威胁你他在威胁你妹妹你会像往常一样逃离自己吗，
I'm really not in the mood right now Sam, Sam, Sam There is a killer on the loose He's threatening you He's threatening your sister Are you gonna run away from who you are like you always do,
还是你要用它?
or are you gonna use it?
我和你不一样真的吗?
I'm not like you Really?
不然你怎么活下去?
And how else are you gonna survive?
要我说，接受你自己，我们走出去，找出是谁干的，然后杀了一些人!
I say accept who you are, let's get out there, find out who's doing this, and cut some fucking throats!
不!
No!
还要额外的毛豆谢谢我十分钟后到再见
And extra edamame Please Thank you I'll be there in ten minutes Bye
老虎,你那?
That you, tiger?
耶稣!
Jesus!
你在外面安全吗，亲爱的?
Are you being safe out there, honey?
以至于我所有的朋友都嘲笑我，是的好孩子-晚餐吃什么?-寿司，我正要去取你为什么不邮寄呢?
To the point that all my friends mock me, yes Good boy - What's for dinner? - Sushi I was just leaving to pick it up Why don't you just Postmates it?
我知道你不喜欢洗个澡我马上就回来-你能帮我把这个收起来吗?——是的
It gets all smooshy by the time it's here I know you hate that Go take a shower I'll be back soon - Can you put this away for me? - Yes
-爱你-爱你-锁门-我会的
-Love you -Love you -Lock the door -I will
-希克斯警长-你好，朱迪警长-你是谁?我想你知道我是恐怖电影的粉丝还有刀子你最喜欢的恐怖电影是什么?
-Sheriff Hicks -Hello, Sheriff Judy - Who is this? - I think you know I'm a fan of scary movies And knives What's your favorite scary movie?
我更喜欢动画电影和音乐剧你为什么要这么做?
I prefer animated films and musicals Why are you doing this?
我会告诉你一切的我打电话来自首我觉得这是个好主意我们在警局坐下来，我会告诉你我杀了两个人的事你只杀了一个人
I'll tell you all about it I'm calling to turn myself in I think that's a great idea We'll sit down at the station, and I'll tell you about the two people I've killed You've only killed one person
等我见到你，我已经把你儿子开膛破肚了
By the time I see you, I'll have gutted your baby boy
去你妈的!
Fuck you!
接,韦斯!
Pick up, Wes!
我是希克斯警长，我需要部队尽快到我家集合收到，我们正在处理
This is Sheriff Hicks I need units to converge on my house ASAP Copy that We're on it
打不通他的电话，是吧?
Can't get him on the phone, can you?
他一定很忙我怎么知道你在他附近?
He must be busy How do I know you're anywhere near him?
看过电影《惊魂记》吗?
Ever seen the movie Psycho?
请……别伤害我的孩子为什么不?
Please... don't hurt my boy Why not?
-他是个好孩子-是吗?
-He's a good kid -Is he, now?
他从没伤害过任何人这还不够求你了!我会做任何事!
He never hurt anyone That's not enough Please! I'll do anything!
你赶不上了，朱迪警长
You're not gonna make it in time, Sheriff Judy
韦斯!
Wes!
我来了!
I'm coming!
韦斯!
Wes!
的帮助!
Help!
好吧
Okay
妈妈?
Mom?
他妈的……你!
Fuck... you!
小姐，你不能在这里你不能在这里不，我很抱歉我认识她的儿子-她的儿子，韦斯他…我很抱歉
Miss, you can't be here You can't be here No, I'm sorry I know her son -Her son, Wes Is he... -I'm sorry
我很抱歉
I'm sorry
对不起
Excuse me
我的天啊你…你是你上次我检查你还好吗?你好像有点小情绪你认识治安官吗?
Oh, my God You're... Well, you're you Last time I checked Are you okay? You seem like you're having a bit of a moment Did you know the sheriff?
有点她不太喜欢我她也不喜欢我我是萨曼莎山姆卡朋特我姐姐和我被袭击了很遗憾我是盖尔…
Sort of She didn't like me very much She didn't like me either I'm Samantha Sam Carpenter My sister and I were attacked Sorry to hear that I'm Gale...
莱利·威瑟斯，我是盖尔·威瑟斯抱歉
Riley Weathers I'm Gale Weathers Excuse me
——盖尔?——一个文本?
- Gale? - A text?
你是说凶手又发短信回来了?
You tell me the killer is back in a text?
-噢，好痛-很好!
-Ow, that hurts -Good!
-你在直播-你怎么知道?
-You were on the air -How do you know?
直觉你看起来不错你还在写作吗?
A hunch You look good Are you still writing?
没有时间你写作的时候总是最开心的先生，没关系的我们和盖尔在一起我很想帮你，但我现在不能放人无法抗拒好故事的诱惑，不是吗?
No time You were always happiest when you were writing Well, sir, it's okay We're here with Gale I'd give you a hand, but I can't release anybody right now Couldn't resist a good story, could you?
别傻了，杜威我来这是因为担心你好吧，是的我的制作人想让我报道这事，原因很明显，但90%都是因为你我感觉90%好多了
Don't be an idiot, Dewey I'm here because I was worried about you Okay, yes My producers wanted me to cover this, for obvious reasons, but 90% is because of you Well, I feel 90% better
别这么敏感你什么时候开始关心我的感受了?尤其是最近几年好吧，听着别假装是我结束了一段感情
Don't be so sensitive Since when did you care about my feelings? Especially not in the last couple years All right, listen Let's not pretend I'm the one who ended things
没人在假装，盖尔我记得发生了什么
No one's pretending, Gale I remember what happened
你怎么没穿制服?
Why aren't you in uniform?
我什么时候退休的?
I retired Since when?
既然他们让我去杜威我不需要你的同情，盖尔我做了我的选择你也一样轮到我了这是个好机会-你说过你会试试的-我试了整整两个月!
Since they asked me to Dewey I don't need your pity, Gale I made my choices So did you It was my turn It was a great opportunity -You said you'd try -And I did For two whole months!
听着，如果你还想让我感觉更糟的话，祝你好运早上没那么糟糕，因为我可以见到你假装我还在纽约但我突然想起…
Listen, if you want to make me feel worse than I already do, good luck The mornings aren't so bad, because I get to see you Pretend I'm still back there in New York But then I remember...
我无法忍受我半夜离开了…像个懦夫一样你为什么不告诉我?
that I couldn't hack it I left in the middle of the night... like a coward Why wouldn't you tell me that then?
这很重要你有很多特质，杜威…
It would have mattered You are a lot of things, Dewey...
但你不是懦夫，你只是…你本该在伍兹伯勒而你却没有?
but you are not a coward You just... You just were meant to be in Woodsboro And you weren't?
答应我你会尽快离开你知道我不能答应你
Promise me you'll leave as soon as you can You know I can't promise that
朱迪的事我很抱歉我也是
I'm sorry about Judy Yeah, me too
但她会成为你下一本书的重要章节
But she'll make a great chapter in your next book
更别提鬼脸的新武器了那玩意点着了我们能谈谈标题吗?刺?跟原版一样吗?
And don't even get me started on Ghostface's signature new weapon That shit is lit And can we talk about the title? Stab? What, just like the original?
就叫它《刺杀8号》吧就是他妈的《刺杀8号》你骗不了任何人简直是胡扯-你去哪了?你还好吗?-我很好
Just call it Stab 8 It's fucking Stab 8 You're not fooling anyone It's such bullshit - Where have you been? Are you okay? - Yeah, I'm fine
那个叫明迪的女孩不是在开玩笑《刺杀8》不像其他的我是说，和其他电影没有任何联系没有任何传统角色这个系列在第五部的时候就出轨了
You know, that Mindy girl wasn't kidding Stab 8 is not like the others I mean, no connection to the other movies No legacy characters at all This franchise goes off the rails with number five
里奇，听我说他又杀了两个人韦斯和他妈妈他杀了警长?你能做到吗?
Richie, listen to me He killed two more people Wes and his mother He killed the sheriff? You can do that?
我是说，你还好吗?你在哪里?
I mean, are you okay? Where are you?
-我马上打给你-不，山姆…我们应该出去找他谁在医院?
-I'll call you right back -No, Sam... We should be out looking for him Who's at the hospital?
谁在照看我妹妹?
Who's watching my sister?
我刚听说警长的事他们需要我!
I just heard about the sheriff They needed me here!
-你要去哪里?-我妹妹有麻烦了!
- Where are you going? - My sister's in trouble!
.．.朱迪·希克斯被残忍杀害的地方
...where Judy Hicks has just been brutally murdered
你还在等什么?
What are you waiting for?
开车!
Drive!
来吧，我们走!
Come on Let's go!
喂?
Hello?
他妈的这
Fuck this
他妈的!
Fuck!
该死的!
Goddamn it!
你现在应该打电话吗?
Should you be making a phone call right now?
请,请
Please, please
停!
Stop!
你知道我们得熬过这一关才能帮她，对吧?
You know we have to live through this to help her, right?
只是坚持
Just hold on
天呐
Holy shit
该死的!
Goddamn it!
里奇?
Richie?
你在这里做什么?
What are you doing here?
山姆打电话来，她说…你有麻烦了-你用电话打我了吗?- - - - - -当心!
Sam called She said that... you were in trouble - Did you hit me with the phone? - Look out!
里奇!
Richie!
-你在医院吗?-你好，萨曼莎不里奇现在不能接电话他正在调查那些在与自己无关的事情上多管闲事的人的下场
- Are you at the hospital? - Hello, Samantha No Richie can't come to the phone right now He's finding out what happens to people who stick their noses in business that doesn't concern them
-请不要伤害他-我告诉你你可以选择我只杀一个什么?塔拉!
-Please don't hurt him -I'll tell you what You can choose I'll only kill one What? Tara!
你想让谁死?
Who do you want to hear die?
不，求你了我求求你别伤害他们真的吗?你连自己的妹妹都救不了?
No, please I'm begging you Please don't hurt them Really? You can't save your own sister?
你只需要说"杀了里奇"
All you have to do is say, "Kill Richie"
不!不!
No! No!
不!塔拉!别碰她求你了，求你了，求你了，我求求你或者说"杀了塔拉"
No! Tara! Don't touch her Please, please, please, I'm begging you Or say, "Kill Tara,"
我保证把上次错过的器官都打一针去你妈的!
and I'll make sure to hit all the organs I missed last time Fuck you!
我求求你不要伤害她拯救一个人的最后机会选择你为什么要这么做?
I'm begging you Please don't hurt her Last chance to save one Choose Why are you doing this?
你想知道为什么吗，萨姆?
You want to know why, Sam?
也许是因为你是个自私的贱人连拯救你爱的人的性命都做不了决定也许你太软弱，不适合这个角色也许你是对的
Maybe it's because you're a selfish bitch who can't even make a decision to save the life of someone you love Maybe you're too weak for this franchise Maybe you're right
或者我只是在拖延时间，混蛋
Or maybe I'm just stalling for time, fuckhead
我去找里奇·塔拉!
I'll get Richie Tara!
来吧，里奇没事的，有我在
Come on, Richie It's okay I got you
一切都会好的
It's gonna be all right
电梯!
Get the elevator!
不是今天
Not today
里奇我们走吧
Richie Let's get out of here
快点，快点
Come on, hurry up
——头部- ?
-The head -What?
你得一枪爆了他们的头，否则他们总会回来的杜威!谁他妈在乎?
You have to shoot 'em in the head, or they always come back Dewey! Who gives a fuck?
我做的-不!杜威!
-I do -No! Dewey!
是的,今天
Yes, today
这是一个荣誉
It's an honor
不!
No!
我很抱歉
I'm sorry
我不太了解他，但是…他帮助了我
I didn't know him well, but... he helped me
他就是这么做的他帮助别人我应该阻止他的如果你阻止了他，我妹妹就死了
That's what he did He helped people I should've stopped him If you had, my sister would be dead
萨曼莎，你妹妹醒了
Samantha, your sister's awake
盖尔西德尼
Gale Sidney
我一听说就赶来了
I came as soon as I heard
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry
你不应该在这里你也不应该在这里
You shouldn't be here You shouldn't be here either
-马克和孩子们没事吧?-是的，他们现在是安全的，我来这里是为了确保这一点过来
- Mark and the kids are okay? - Yeah, they're safe for now I'm here to make sure of that Come here
你感觉如何?
How you feeling?
每次我被攻击，他们就会给我更好的止痛药就这样
Every time I get attacked, they give me better painkillers So there's that
对不起什么?你救了我的命
I'm sorry For what? You saved my life
因为没有早点告诉你因为你是爸爸离开的原因你不是爸爸离开的原因你没有选择你从哪里来或者你从哪里来我不怪你
For not telling you sooner For being the reason Dad left You're not the reason Dad left You didn't choose where you came from Or who you came from I don't blame you for that
我也怪你离开了我这不会再发生了，我知道
I blame you for leaving me too That's never gonna happen again I know
那你当时为什么不来找我?
But why didn't you come to me back then?
我本可以帮忙的因为…
I could've helped Because...
我害怕什么?
I was scared Of what?
我害怕自己会变成他那样所以我跑去保护你-远离我-山姆…你永远不可能像他一样
I was scared that I would turn out just like him So I ran To protect you -From me -Sam... you could never be like him
你现在太兴奋了我现在太兴奋了我不打算撒谎
-You're so high right now -I'm so high right now I'm not even gonna lie
我爱你，我也爱你
I love you I love you too
那我们现在怎么办?
So what do we do now?
在这种情况下没人会这么做我们要离开伍兹伯勒
What nobody ever does in these situations We're gonna get the fuck out of Woodsboro
——这是她吗?- - -是的
- That's her? - Yeah
萨曼莎?
Samantha?
我是萨姆，我是……-我知道你是谁
It's Sam - I'm... - I know who you are
我希望你没事-听着，对不起…-你是比利的女儿我们把车开过来
I hope you're okay - Listen, I'm sorry... - You're Billy's daughter We'll bring the car around
是啊，我是他女儿如果这让你觉得奇怪，我很抱歉不，不，这是…我已经经历了很多你想谈谈吗?
Yeah I'm his daughter I'm sorry if that's weird for you No, no, it's... I've been through this A lot You want to talk?
我很感激而且我…杜威的事我真的很抱歉但我要把我妹妹从这一切中带走
I appreciate it And I'm... I'm really sorry about Dewey But I'm taking my sister away from all this
我也试过逃跑但不管用，总是这样恕我直言，那是你的生活，不是我的-我不太确定-你想从我这里得到什么，女士?
I tried running too It doesn't work, it always follows All due respect, that's your life, not mine -I'm not so sure about that -What do you want from me, lady?
嘿!注意你的语气，新来的你知道他们总是说要回到原来的样子吗?
Hey! Watch your tone, new girl You know how they always say it goes back to the original?
这是最初的想法我想要你的帮助因为你错了，这是你的生活也就是说这个人会一直来找你-所以呢?-所以我要你帮我们杀了他
Here's the original I want your help Because you're wrong, this is your life now Which means whoever this is will keep coming for you - So? - So I want you to help us kill him
你想让我帮你和一个早间节目的主持人杀人?
You want me to help you and the host of a morning show commit murder?
-没错-在这种情况下我是什么?
-Correct -Yeah And I'm what in this scenario?
诱饵吗?无助的受害者?
The bait? The helpless victim?
-如果合适的话…-你不是无助的，山姆他杀了你的朋友，也杀了我们的我有孩子，所以他不入土我是不会睡觉的
-If the shoe fits... -You're not helpless, Sam He killed your friend, he killed ours And I have kids, which means I won't sleep until he's in the ground
听着，我很抱歉这件事对你们的生活造成了影响但不管你，凶手或其他人怎么说，这不是我的故事好吧!我们离开这鬼地方吧?
Look, I'm sorry about what this has done to your lives But no matter what you or the killer or anyone says, this isn't my story All right! Let's get the fuck out of town, huh?
抱歉这是我男朋友，里奇很高兴见到你…我们遇见了山姆，请上车，这样我们就再也不用见到这些人了-山姆…-不我们要走了这是我能保护塔拉的唯一办法
Sorry That's my boyfriend, Richie Nice to meet... We met Sam, please get in the car so we never have to see these people again - Sam... - No We're leaving That's the only way I can protect Tara
好吧,祝你好运
Okay, good luck
你也
You too
那真是太他妈糟糕了别担心，我有个计划她看起来很坚强老实说，希德，谁在乎?
Well, that went fucking horribly Don't worry, I have a plan She seems really tough Honestly, Sid, who gives a shit?
你自己说的，他会去找她我在她车上装了追踪器你做了什么?
You said it yourself, he's gonna go after her I put a tracker on her car You did what?
这似乎是盖尔·威瑟斯会做的事把这当成是恭维我给妈妈留了言我告诉她我们要去哪里你还好吧?
It seemed like something Gale Weathers would do Take that as a compliment I left a message for Mom I told her where we're going You good back there?
妈的，在哪儿?
Fuck, where is it?
什么在哪里?
Where's what?
我的吸入器我通常多留一个我们应该回去吗?
My inhaler I usually keep an extra one Should we go back?
哇，好吧，我投票赞成不回谋杀医院-你想去药店吗?-我需要一张处方但我在安柏家多留了一张她马上就来不…没有
Whoa Okay I vote for not going back to the murder hospital - You want to stop at a pharmacy? - I'd need a prescription But I left an extra one at Amber's Her house is on the way No... no
你能坚持到莫德斯托吗?
I'd be in and out Could you hold out till Modesto?
-我不这么认为-好吧，地址是什么?
-I don't think so -Okay, what's the address?
123没有该死的路，里奇，她需要它我需要把所有的血都留在我的身体里你也需要，里奇，拜托没事的好吧，是的该死的地址是什么?
123 No Fucking Way Lane Richie, she needs it And I need to keep all the blood inside my body So do you Richie, please It's okay Okay, yeah Fuck What's the goddamn address?
谢谢你能来
Hey, thanks for coming
继续倒，惠勒谢谢你嘿，韦斯!
Keep pouring, Wheeler Thank you Hey To Wes!
漂亮的狗娘养的我们爱你，伙计!
Beautiful son of a bitch We love you, buddy!
照片,是真的吗?这应该是一个追悼会我就是这样哀悼和转移自己对死亡的恐惧的注意力的嘿，我们的啤酒不够了地下室还有我去拿
Shots, really? This is supposed to be a memorial Well, this is how I mourn and distract myself from the looming specter of Death Hey, we're low on beer There's more in the basement I'll go get some
搞什么，明迪?耶稣!
What the fuck, Mindy? Jesus!
那是一个测试，你失败了永远不要独自一人和一个蒙面杀手在一起你是那个说我们需要更多啤酒的人你应该叫我和你一起去的
That was a test And you failed Never go off on your own with a masked killer around You're the one that said we needed more beer And you should have asked me to come with you
你知道当周围有蒙面杀手时你还不该做什么吗?
You know what else you shouldn't do when there's a masked killer around?
什么?
What?
我是说，一个人跟着某人进了一个黑暗、恐怖的地下室……你怎么知道我不是凶手?
Follow someone into a dark, creepy basement alone I mean... how do you know I'm not the killer?
因为我
Because I am
我没有，实际上但是让这成为一个教训不要相信任何人你说你不是凶手，我怎么能相信你?
I'm not, actually But let that be a lesson Don't trust anyone Then how can I trust you when you say you're not the killer?
没错你在学现在我们回楼上去
Exactly You're learning Now let's go back upstairs
你先来，很好
You first Very good
我想我准备好了我是说，我想我们应该现在你想上楼吗?
I think I'm ready I mean, I think we should Like now You want to go upstairs?
喜欢……像楼上吗?
Like... Like upstairs?
嗯现在
Uh-huh Right now
别误会我的意思，但我想我得放弃这个什么?
Don't take this the wrong way, but I think I have to pass on that What?
为什么?
Why?
你知道，我不太确定你不是…"别误会我的意思"
You know, I'm not like entirely sure that you're not the... killer "Don't take this the wrong way"?
不，不，听着，我几乎百分百确定你不是，但是…最安全的选择是和所有人待在一起…去你妈的…潜在的证人
No, no, look I'm almost 100% certain that you are not, but... the safest option is to be down here with all the people... Fuck you ...and the potential witnesses
这是一种完全合理的情绪反应-也是-该死的混蛋干得好，明迪如果我没有写那本关于你母亲的书，-这一切都不会发生-盖尔
That is a completely valid emotional response to have -That too -Fucking asshole Good job Fuck you, Mindy If I hadn't have written that book about your mother, -none of this would've happened -Gale
-我挑起了这一切-不，你没有比利·卢米斯挑起了这一切，我们要结束这一切今晚之后，不要再读书，不要再看电影，不要再看鬼脸了
-I started all of this -No, you didn't Billy Loomis started this, and we're gonna end it After tonight, no more books, no more movies, no more fucking Ghostface
-你不知道规矩吗?什么规则?
- Don't you know the rules? - What rules?
要想在恐怖电影中幸存下来是有特定规则的比如，第一，你不能做爱-别这么做-别出去追她-她不会回我短信的
There are specific rules to successfully survive a horror movie For instance, Number One: You can never have sex -Don't do it Don't go outside after her -She's not texting me back
因为她很可能已经死了天哪，明迪那是我女朋友，我爱她是你女朋友吗你就打算坐着看一部关于我们叔叔被捅的电影?
Because she's probably dead Jesus, Mindy That's my girlfriend, and I love her Was your girlfriend You're just gonna sit and watch a movie about our uncle getting stabbed?
这能让我平静下来，好吗?
It calms me down, okay?
我还会抽点大麻，可能还会和弗朗西丝勾搭上玩得开心哦，天哪，至少带点武器来吧
I'm also gonna smoke some weed and possibly hook up with Frances Have fun Oh, my God, at least take some sort of weapon Here you go
好吧
All right
什么?
What?
丽芙·?
Liv?
好吧好吧，不该死!
All right Okay, yeah, no Shit!
他妈的!
Fuck!
请,请,请
Please, please, please
哇!停!等等!
Whoa! Stop! Wait!
太好了，她在开派对谁在杀人狂欢中开派对?我要取消计划不，我们已经到了，我马上进去拿我五分钟后回来，我也来
Perfect She's having a party Who has a party in the middle of a killing spree? I'm aborting the plan No, we're already here I'll go in quickly and get it I'll be back in five I'm coming too
如果你认为我在外面等着被人谋杀，那你就疯了
If you think I'm waiting out here just to get murdered, you're out of your mind
塔拉!
Tara!
你出医院做什么?你应该起来走动走动吗?
What are you doing out of the hospital? Should you even be up and around?
-我需要我的备用吸入器-为什么?你要去哪里?
-I need my spare inhaler -Why? Where are you going?
没事的，别告诉我我明白了安全点，好吗?
It's fine, don't tell me I get it Just be safe, okay?
我想它在我房间里好了，各位!谢谢你来，但是派对结束了!
I think it's in my room All right, everyone! Thanks for coming, but the party's over!
-该走了!——不!
- Time to go! - No!
可现在还早呢!
But it's so early!
让我们去
Let's go
嘿,嘿,嘿!你好!能把音乐关掉吗?
Hey, hey, hey! Hello! Can we cut the music, please?
嗨……Z世代你好吗?
Hi... Gen Z How are you?
山姆和泰拉都被凶手袭击过两次现在他们来了，这地方成了巨大的谋杀目标，所以…如果我是你，我可能会离开
Both Sam and Tara here have been attacked by the killer twice Now they're here, which makes this place a huge murder target, so... if I were you, I would probably leave
好吧，我想对你友好点给我滚出去!
Okay, I tried to be nice Get the fuck out!
请滚出去-真心的，滚出去-扫兴鬼!
Please get the fuck out -Sincerely, get the fuck out -Buzzkill!
谢谢谢谢大家我保证我会救你们的命谢谢，孩子们
Thank you Thank you all I'm saving your life I promise Thanks, teens
非常感谢很好，谢谢你离开杯子谢谢你救命我在救你的命救你的命，谢谢第三:
Thank you so much Great, thank you for leaving the cup Thank you Saving your life I'm saving your life Saving your life, thank you And Number Three:
在任何情况下都不要说:“我马上就回来。”
Never, ever, ever, under any circumstances, say, "I'll be right back"
因为你回不来了某人的傻逼老爸把我们赶出去了该死的谢谢谢谢，伙计们，晚安-你有我的号码拜拜
'Cause you won't be back Somebody's goofy-ass dad's kicking us out Goddamn it Thank you Thanks, guys, have a good night -You have my number Bye -Bye
嗨，还有啤酒吗?厨房里没有是的，里奇，地下室有啤酒就在你身后地下室是的你想和我一起去吗?
Hi Is there any beer left? There's none in the kitchen Yes, Richie, there's beer in the basement Right behind you Basement Yeah Do you want to come with me?
不但是你问得对是的
No But you were right to ask Yeah
好的，我马上回来
Okay, I'll be right back
是啊，是啊他死了他妈的优步取消了我的预约!
Yeah Yeah Well, he's dead The goddamn fucking Uber canceled on me!
太好了现在我不能做爱，也不能搭车回家了今晚还有比这更糟糕的吗?
Great Now I can't have sex and I can't get a ride home Could this night get any shittier?
丽芙，我弟弟呢?
Liv, where's my brother?
什么?我不知道，明迪可能是在指责每个人都是凶手!
What? I don't know, Mindy Probably off accusing everyone of being the killer!
他真的去找你了我没看到他好吗?
He actually went looking for you I didn't see him Okay?
你为什么这样看着我?
Why are you looking at me like that?
只是在修改我的嫌疑人名单
Just revising my suspect list
他妈的!
Fuck this!
你怕我吗，明蒂?
Are you afraid of me, Mindy?
你觉得我对你弟弟做了什么吗?嗯?
You think I did something to your brother? Huh?
你觉得我会…把你?
You think I'm gonna... cut you up?
现在有一点了……是啊，我记得你说过我太无趣了，不适合当杀手也许这就是转折你觉得呢?你是专家你知道专家最后会怎么样吗?
A little bit now... yeah I thought you said I was too boring to be the killer Maybe that's the twist What do you think, huh? You're the expert You know what eventually happens to the expert?
什么?
What?
享受你那愚蠢的电影吧
Enjoy your stupid movie
该死的疯子他们停了-加油站?-不-哦，该死的-什么?
Fucking psycho They stopped - Gas station? - No -Oh, shit -What?
哦，该死我们还有多远?
Oh, shit How far are we?
太过分了该死，泰拉，我们要走了!
Too far Damn it Tara, we're leaving!
喂你必须马上离开那所房子你怎么知道我在哪里?
Hello You need to get out of that house right now How do you know where I am?
你在斯图·马赫的家里，在那里你爸爸和斯图杀了所有人有人计划把你送到那里你他妈快滚，萨姆!
You're in Stu Macher's house, where your dad and Stu killed everyone Someone planned to get you there You need to get the fuck out, Sam!
不，杰米小心小心，杰米你知道他在附近-什么?-他来了快点，伙计，转过去!转身!老兄!
No, Jamie Watch out Watch out, Jamie You know he's around - What? - There he is Come on, man, turn around! Turn around! Dude!
我告诉过你，我告诉过你，他就在拐角处杰米-看你后面-不，兰迪，看你后面快点，伙计，转过去!
I told you I told you, he's around the corner Jamie -Look behind you -No, Randy, look behind you Come on, man, turn around!
伙计，你在干什么?你能做到的!
Dude, what are you doing? You can do it!
这是你的规则!承认你身后的那坨屎!回头看看后面……哦,狗屎!
These are your rules! Own that shit Behind you! Turn around Look behind... Oh, shit!
你流了很多血，山姆不，明迪，坚持住-你对她做了什么?-没什么不，我什么都没做-凶手，他…-她还好吗?
That's a lot of blood, Sam No, Mindy, stay with me - What did you do to her? - Nothing No, I didn't do anything - The killer, he... - Is she okay?
他妈的什么?
What the fuck?
里奇，你他妈去哪了?
Richie, where the fuck were you?
我去地下室拿啤酒你一个人去地下室?
I went into the basement to get beer You went to the basement alone?
我叫她跟我一起来的!她说不!
I asked her to come with me! She said no!
他妈的!
Fuck!
滚远点，上帝!
Stay the fuck back Jesus Christ!
我当时和泰拉在一起，但你们其他人都在闲逛你们其中一个就是凶手!
I was with Tara, but the rest of you were wandering around One of you is the fucking killer!
去你妈的，安柏去你妈的!
Fuck you, Amber Fuck you!
-你手上为什么有血?——什么?
- Why is there blood on your hands? - What?
-我找到查德了，我找到查德了，他…——乍得?
- I found Chad I found Chad and he's... - Chad?
-你他妈的在撒谎-不-你是凶手-不，我不是丽芙，住手-去你妈的!-丽芙，别说了!
-You're fucking lying -No -You're the killer -No, I'm not Liv, stop - Fuck you! - Liv, just stop!
去你妈的，安柏我他妈不是凶手!
Fuck you, Amber I'm not the fucking killer!
我知道
I know
欢迎来到第三幕，奔跑!
Welcome to Act Three Run!
神圣的狗屎!
Holy shit!
山姆,加油!
Sam, come on!
快跑!走,走,走!走吧!
Run! Go, go, go! Go!
-我的天啊…塔拉!-等等，不，山姆她有枪总是有两个杀手
- Oh, my God... Tara! - Wait, no, Sam She has a gun There are always two killers
山姆，请把刀放下
Sam, please put the knife down
看,我认为……-我觉得另一个凶手可能是塔拉-什么?
Look, I think... -I think the other killer might be Tara -What?
是她把我们带到这里来的，而你们俩已经疏远多年了，我是说…你到底有多了解她?
She's the one that brought us here and you two have been estranged for years I mean... how well do you really know her?
比我更了解你
Better than I know you
山姆,等山姆!
Sam, wait Sam!
听起来不错准备好了吗?
Sounds about right You ready?
对于这个吗?我们走吧
For this? Never Here we go
救我，救我!他捅我!
Help me, help me! He stabbed me!
-你觉得呢?-陷阱，操!
- What do you think? - Trap Fuck it Ow!
大风!大风!
Gale! Gale!
等等，让我看看-你要去医院-不你说过我们会完成的去完成它，西德尼·盖尔为了杜威
Wait Let me see -You got to go to the hospital -No You said we were gonna finish this Go finish it, Sidney Gale For Dewey
任何躲藏的人，不管是不是凶手，给你们五秒钟现身!
Anyone hiding, killer or not, you have five seconds to show yourself!
我的天啊
Tara Oh, my God
山姆山姆,请
Sam Sam, please
你好,西德尼!
Hello, Sidney!
你好，你去哪了?
Hello there Where'd you go?
这不是安柏，我是另一个你们有两个人再说一次，我以前看过这部电影不是这部电影，西德尼你真的需要点新素材我给你找来的，不是吗?
This isn't Amber I'm the other one There's two of you Again I've seen this movie before Not this movie, Sidney You really need some new material I got you here, didn't I?
你可能是最具衍生性的我是说，天哪，同一栋房子?
You might actually be the most derivative one of all I mean, Christ, the same house?
也许是吧但你忘了在电影《刺杀》中幸存的第一条规则-永远不要回答…-我很无聊等等!
Maybe so But you forgot the first rule of surviving a Stab movie - Never answer the... - I'm bored Wait!
举起手来!举起手来!你在里面干什么?
Put your hands up! Show me your hands! What are you doing in there?
躲着杀人犯我叫你出来!
Hiding from murderers I told you to come out!
我不会出来的!你拍摄一切!
I'm not gonna come out! You're shooting everything!
该死，是幽灵脸!
Holy shit, it's Ghostface!
里奇!枪拿枪有点难，因为你打中了我的腿
Richie! Gun Get the gun Kind of hard since you shot me in the leg
——是的!是的!——他开枪!
- Yes! Yes! - Shoot him!
谢天谢地，你没事
Thank God you're okay
因为我真的真的很想杀了你
'Cause I really, really wanted to be the one to kill you
给我坐下，普雷斯科特!
Sit the fuck down, Prescott!
真不敢相信这招管用了
I can't believe this worked
我知道这很扫兴，是我
I know It's a bummer it's me
但这确实是电影的最佳选择
But it really was the best choice for the movie
这又不是电影!
This isn't a fucking movie!
不但是会的-这就是重点，对吧，安柏?——对,亲爱的!
No But it will be - That's the point, right, Amber? - Right, hon!
第三幕血洗，检查杀手揭露，检查时间大结局!
Third Act bloodbath, check Killers revealed, check Time for the big finale!
里奇…
Richie...
好了，好了我们把他们弄到厨房去走吧，婊子!
Okay Okay Let's get 'em into the kitchen Let's go, bitch!
总得有人来拯救这个系列你知道吗，自从第一部之后就没人拍过很棒的《刺杀》电影了不是真的宝贝，你想去找前莱利夫人吗?
Someone has to save the franchise You see, no one has made a great Stab movie since the first one Not really Hey, baby, you want to go get the very ex-Mrs Riley?
是的，我知道嘿，嘿!
Yeah, I do Hey, hey!
哇……西德尼·普雷斯科特你知道…我是你的超级粉丝去你妈的-你看了《刺杀》的最后一部吗?-我不是恐怖电影的粉丝这已经证实了不管怎样，这电影烂透了
Whoa... whoa Sidney Prescott You know... I'm a really big fan Go fuck yourself - You see the last Stab movie? - Not really a fan of scary movies That checks out Anyway, it sucked balls
因为没人把真正的粉丝当回事不是真的他们只是嘲笑我们，为什么?
Because nobody takes the true fans seriously Not really They just laugh at us, and why?
因为我们爱某样东西?
Because we love something?
我们对他们来说只是个笑话吗?
We're just a fucking joke to them?
粉丝怎么会是有毒的呢?
How can fandom be toxic?
这是关于爱情的!
It's about love!
他们不明白这些电影对人们的重要性-里奇…-但我们要帮助他们!
They don't fucking understand that these movies are important to people -Richie... -But we're gonna help them!
好莱坞完全没主意了，所以我们决定给他们一些新的素材让他们回归本原因为只有这样才能拍出一部很棒的《刺杀》，山姆
Hollywood's totally fucking out of ideas, so we decided we'd give them some new source material to follow Bring it back to basics Because that's how you make a great Stab movie, Sam
“根据实际事件”
"Based on actual events"
-盖尔-给我坐下!
-Gale -Sit the fuck down!
备份
Back up
你做这一切就为了让我成为你那部烂电影的英雄吗?
You did all this just to make me the hero of your fucked-up movie?
亲爱的，你不是英雄
Sweetie, you're not the hero
你是恶棍比利·卢米斯的女儿看到了她死去父亲的幻象西德尼·普雷斯科特杀了你父亲你…就为了让她回伍兹伯勒吗
You're the villain The daughter of Billy Loomis who sees fucked-up visions of her dead dad Sidney Prescott killed your father You... did all this just to get her back to Woodsboro
你知道《刺杀》系列电影最大的问题是什么吗?
You know what the biggest problem with the Stab movies is?
没有迈克尔·迈尔斯和杰森·沃希没有坏人会回来但是最初的策划者的私生女?
There's no Michael Myers or Jason Voorhees No bad guy to keep coming back But the illegitimate daughter of the original mastermind?
那他妈就是个坏蛋-你怎么知道的?-关于你父亲?
Now that's a fucking villain - How did you know? - About your father?
这是个小镇，你妈又是个酒鬼!
It's a small town and your mom's a drunk!
我是在红迪网上"刺杀"版块认识里奇的自从我父母买了这房子后我就一直沉迷其中我们很快就意识到我们有相似的想法我在莫德斯托找到你并不难
I met Richie on the Stab subreddit I've been obsessed ever since my parents bought this house We realized pretty quickly we had similar ideas Wasn't that hard for me to find you in Modesto
对我来说，操你也不是那么难但我想，现在做一个有性欲的女人应该是有力量的去你的!
It wasn't that hard for me to fuck you, either But I guess being a sexually available woman is supposed to be empowering these days Fuck you!
好吧，现在你只是引用了原著但这对你来说是行不通的，山姆看，我们必须把那些传统角色带回来，这样才有意义
Well, now you're just quoting the original But it wouldn't work with just you, Sam See, we had to bring the legacy characters back to make it matter
没有杰米·李就没法过真正的万圣节!
Can't have a bona fide Halloween without Jamie Lee!
不!
Nope!
杜威必须死才能让它成真证明这不是什么狗屁，赚钱的，普通的续集因为我们的电影有赌注!
Dewey had to die to make it real To show that this wasn't just some bullshit, cash-in, run-of-the-mill sequel Because our movie has fucking stakes!
因为任何人都可能在魔咒中死去不!
'Cause anyone can die in a requel No!
该死的哇，哇!
Goddamn it Whoa, whoa!
不,嘿!给我坐下
No, hey! Sit the fuck down
我很抱歉，希德我们也不能让你活着我是说，这么多次活下来…那就太荒谬了这次是球迷赢了
I'm so sorry, Sid We can't let you live, either I mean, surviving this many times... that would just be ridiculous This time the fans are gonna be the ones who win
-这就够了吗?-搞定了，宝贝把塔拉弄出来我们得开始准备尸体了!
- That about cover it? - Nailed it, baby Get Tara out of the closet We got to start staging the bodies!
坚持住，希德坚持住你真应该听杜威的话他一鸣惊人!伙计，看看那个爱慕对象!
Stay with me, Sid Stay with me You really should've listened to Dewey He nailed it in one! Dude, look at the love interest!
你他妈傻吗?
Are you fucking stupid?
我甚至让你相信那可能是你妹妹
I even had you convinced it could be your sister
她不在这儿
She's not here
你他妈什么意思，她不在这儿?
What the fuck do you mean, she's not here?
她不在这里!
She's not here!
我给她松绑了看来你没你想的那么有说服力
I untied her Guess you're not as persuasive as you thought
这是给你的是啊，就像你的瘸腿小妹妹会有所作为一样她现在是我们的坐垫安布尔!散开她不可能走远的——我找不到她!
That's for you Yeah, like your gimpy little sister's gonna make a difference She's our fucking pincushion at this point Amber! Fan out She couldn't have gotten far I can't find her!
琥珀吗?
Amber?
山姆!你要去哪里?你的大场面就要来了!
Sam! Where you going? Your big scene's coming up!
他妈的杀了你!
Fucking kill you!
他妈的洗手液?
The fucking hand sanitizer?
不不不，这不是我的错!这不是我的错!
No, no, no, it's not my fault! It's not my fault!
让我猜猜，是电影让你这么做的?
Let me guess, the movies made you do it?
不，是留言板的问题!我被激进化了-被影迷?-是的，他们很生气!
No, it was the message boards! I was radicalized - By movie fans? - Yes, they're so mad!
拜托，这不是我的错，我只是个傻孩子我想参与一些事"参与一些事"?你杀了我最好的朋友!
Please, it's not my fault I'm just a dumb kid I wanted to be a part of something "A part of something"? You killed my best friend!
是啊，他死得像个娘们
Yeah, and he died like a pussy
这就是杀人狂的特点，山姆
That's the thing about slashers, Sam
这么多血迹都是你的?
So many blood trails This one yours?
只有一个办法能知道!
Only one way to find out!
我也是杜威死前看到的最后一样东西我真不敢相信我能对你们俩下手这次不会在最后关头救你们你的故事结束了!
I was the last thing Dewey saw before he died too I can't believe I get to do you both No last-minute saves this time Your story's over!
该把火炬传递给你了，婊子!
Time to pass the torch It's all yours, bitch!
-你想做这个吗?-这个是你的
- You want to do the honors? - This one's yours
不，停，停，停!杜威的事我很抱歉去你妈的
No, stop, stop, stop! I'm sorry about Dewey Fuck you
享受这样的火炬
Enjoy that torch
停止……该死的…我的结局!
Stop... fucking up... my ending!
山姆?
Sam?
山姆!
Sam!
好吧
Okay
你现在打算怎么办?
What are you gonna do now, huh?
给我打个恐怖的电话?
Make a scary phone call to me?
戴着鬼脸面具从壁橱里出来?
Pop out of that closet in a Ghostface mask?
不，因为你是恶棍!
No Because you're the villain!
最后坏人死了这就是规则我要引入一个新规则那是什么规则?嗯?
And the villain dies at the end Those are the rules I'm introducing a new rule And what would that be? Huh?
好吗?
Well?
永远不要和连环杀手的女儿乱搞
Never fuck with the daughter of a serial killer
是什么……我的结局?
What about... my ending?
它来了
Here it comes
小心，他们总会回来的
Careful, they always come back
好吧,然后
Okay, then
我还是更喜欢《巴巴杜》
I still prefer The Babadook
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
你是好吗?
Are you good?
我很抱歉借过借过，先生
I'm so sorry Excuse me Excuse me, sir
-嘿-嘿她会没事的
-Hey -Hey She's gonna be okay
这次你能带我们去另一家医院吗?
Can you take us to a different hospital this time?
当然
Of course
准备好了吗?
You ready to go?
我马上回来，好吗?
I'll be right back, yeah?
你的生命体征还好你等着抽风，好吗?
Your vitals look good You sit tight for a draft, okay?
西德尼·盖尔
Sidney Gale
谢谢你们俩所做的一切你们没事吧?
Thank you both For everything Are you gonna be all right?
我会活下来的我一直都是你是对的…我很抱歉
I'll survive I always do You were right... about not running Sorry about that
你还好吗?
How are you doing?
过几天再问我但至少我知道我要写些什么那是什么?
Ask me in a few days But at least I know what I'm gonna write about What's that?
不是这个那些混蛋可以匿名死但也许是关于一个曾经在这里当过治安官的好人的故事我很想读读那篇报道
Not this Those fuckers can die in anonymity But maybe something about a good man who used to be the sheriff here once I'd like to read that story
我能问你个奇怪的问题吗?
Can I ask you a weird question?
是的，我没事吧?
Yeah Am I gonna be okay?
最终
Eventually
嘿，等等，山姆，山姆!
Hey Wait Sam, Sam!
谢谢你！
Thank you
没有我你哪儿也去不了别担心，我会一直牵着你的手
Well, you're not going anywhere without me Don't worry I'm gonna hold your hand all the way there
我可以照顾她和她妹妹她已经准备好被送走了
I can take care of her and her sister She's all ready for transportation
25年前，差不多就在今天，在这所房子里一个悲惨的故事结束了今晚，新的篇章结束了警方现在没有很多信息，
25 years ago, almost to the day, in this very house a tragic story ended Tonight, a new chapter came to a close Police do not have a lot of information right now,
他们还在收集证据如你所见，这是一个非常活跃的犯罪现场死亡人数不详，多人受伤，
as they are still collecting evidence As you can see, this is a very active crime scene An unknown number of fatalities, several injuries,
就在我们说话的时候有人被救护车带走了这是一个正在发展的故事…
some people being taken off by ambulance right now as we speak This is a developing story...